searchbytes.com 2003-12-08

# Searchbytes

Home : Privacy

1\. All information collected as a result of your membership in Searchbytes will be controlled by Searchbytes. Searchbytes may transfer and share your information within the Searchbytes group of international affiliated entities ("Searchbytes Group") as part of a transfer of your membership agreement. We will do this to improve the administration of the services. At all times the companies that make up the Searchbytes Group ("We") will follow this privacy policy.

2\. We give, sell, rent, share, or trade any identifiable personal information regarding our members to third party with your permission, with the exception of third-party contractors and service providers who work with Searchbytes to provide the Software, and other services, and who are strictly prohibited from later use of the information that they may have access to.

3\. Bussearch may share non-personal aggregate, or summary, information regarding its members with partners or other third parties. We can - and you authorize us to - disclose personal information to local, state, or federal law enforcement officials when required to do so by public authorities or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.

4\. In our online registration form, we require you to provide us with your full name, full street address, email address, a password, and other demographic information. We will process this information to administer your membership, to provide the Advertisement Service and other services to you and to provide you with the full benefits of membership as detailed below.

5\. Information required for Tax Purposes Related to the Advertisement Service. If You join the Advertisement Service and accuire US $600 in your account we may contact you to request additional information including, for example, the Social Security number of our U.S. Members or confirmation of country of residence for non-US members. We will only use this additional information for legitimate purposes related to complying with applicable tax laws. If You are contacted and fail to provide us with the information we legitimately require, we may refuse to pay You until we receive that information.

6\. In addition to uses of Your information described above, Searchbytes may use Your information in the following ways:

  * We may use your email address to verify your identity and protect against fraud and to contact you any time and as many times as it takes. In addition, we may use it to send you updates about your account, new products and services, and company updates. If you participate in the Advertisement Service, we will use the address information for various matters, including for verification of your location for tax purposes. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address may also be used to gather broad demographic information.
  * We may process the information You provide to us to build a profile of your interests and activities so that we can send you advertisements, offers, benefits and content targeted at your specific interests, and to provide you with the full benefits of membership. As we aggregate thistype of information about all of our members, we offer summaries to our advertisers and other interested parties so that they can learn what products and services are most popular to consumers, but we do not disclose our members' names, addresses, or other personally identifiable information (except email addresses with your permission) to these third parties.
  * Searchbytes maintains its records in the United States as well as countries outside of the United States. Accordingly, Searchbytes may transfer your personal data internationally to other countries. Some of the countries may have laws that protect personal data, some may not. Searchbytes will try to protect your information no matter where we process or store your data by following this privacy statement and by complying with the relevant data protection laws in force in your country. We will also oblige our third party contractors to comply with those laws. By becoming a Member you give your consent to this transfer of your personal data.
  * Searchbytes may transfer or share your information within the Searchbytes Group as part of a transfer of your membership agreement. It will, for example, do this in order to improve the administration of the Searchbytes services. At all times the Searchbytes Group will follow this privacy policy and ensure the security and confidentiality of personal data.

7\. The Software includes the opportunity for You to establish links to other Web sites. Searchbytes is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

8\. Searchbytes Web site will try to protect from the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Unfortunately, when you submit information about yourself to Searchbytes over the Internet the information may travel over many systems that are not under the control of Searchbytes. The Internet is not 100% secure and others may intercept the information that you are sending. One easy and important way to protect your personal information is to guard your account password and close your browser when you step away from your computer.

9\. To update your contact or address information, please use the Account Update Form.

10\. Searchbytes wants to help parents protect the privacy of children and will take steps to obtain parental permission before children may begin the Advertisement Service. Searchbytes does not consider our Web site or the Advertisement Service to be directed at children but some children may have signed up as Members. Please contact us!
